BLACK SCREEN
These are dark time there is no denying.
Our world has prehaps faced no greater threat than it does today.
But I say this to our citizens.
We, ever your servants ...
will continue to defend you liberty
and repel the forces that seek to take it from you.
Your ministry remains strong.
Hermione, tea is ready, Darling.
Coming, Mom!
Come on! Dudley hurry up.
I still don't understand why we have to leave?
Because it's not safe around here anymore.
Ron, tell your father suppers nearly ready.
- She's so strong here. - Mm, she's wonderful isn't it.
Obliviate.
Severus, I was beginning to worry you had lost your way.
Come, we have saved you a seat.
Do you bring news, I trust.
It will happen Saturday, next. At night fall.
I've heard differently my lord.
Dawlish, the auror has let slip that the Potter boy,
will not be moved until the 30th of this month.
The day before he turns 17.
This is a false trail.
The auror office no longer
plays any part in the protection of Harry Potter.
Those closest to him believe we have infiltrated the Ministry.
Well, they got that right, didn't they.
What say you, Pius?
One hears many things, my lord.
Whether the truth is among them, is not clear.
Spoken like a true politician.
You will I think prove most useful, Pius.
Where will he be taken, the boy?
To a safe house.
Most likely the home of someone in the Order.
I'm told its been given every manner of protection possible.
Once there it will be impractical to attack him
My lord,
I'd like to volunteer myself for this task.
I want to kill the boy.
Wormtail!
Have I not spoken to you about keeping our guest quiet?
Yes, my lord.
Right away, my lord.
As inspiring as I find your bloodlust, Bellatrix.
I must be the one to kill Harry Potter.
But I face an unfortunate complication.
That my wand and Potters share the same core.
They are, in some ways,
twins.
We can wound but not fatally harm one another.
If I am to kill him,
I must do it with another's wand.
Come, surely one of you would like the honor.
What about you, Lucius?
- My lord? - "My Lord"?
I require your wand.
- Do I detect elm? - Yes, my Lord.
And the core?
- Dragon heartstring, my lord. - Dragon heartstring?
To those of you who do not know,
we are joined tonight by
Miss Charity Burbage.
Who until recently taught
at Hogwarts School of witchcraft and wizardry
Her specialty was muggle studies
It is Miss Burbage's belief
that Muggles are not so different from us.
She would, given her way,
have us mate with them.
To her the mixture of magical and Muggle blood
is not an abomination,
but something, to be encouraged.
Severus.
Severus, please.
We're friends.
Nagini.
Dinner.
Hello, Harry!
- Hello! - You're looking fit.
Yeah, he's absolutely gorgeous...
I say lets get undercover, before someone murders him.
Evening.
Kingsley, I thought you were looking after the Prime Minister?
You are more important.
Hello Harry. Bill Weasley.
Oh, pleasure to meet you.
- He wasn't always so handsome - Daredevil.
True enough.
Caught one in Wales,
name of Greyback
I think I'll favor him one day.
Oh you're still beautiful to me, William.
Must remember,
Fleur Bill takes his steak on the raw side now.
My husband the joker.
By the way, wait till you hear the news,
Reamus and I...
All right then, time for a cozy catch up later.
We've got to get the hell out of here. And soon.
Potter, you're underage,
which means you've still got the trace on you.
What's the trace?
If you sneezed,
the Ministry will know who wipes your nose.
The point is we have to use
those means of transport the trace can't detect.
Brooms, thestrals and the bike. We'll go in pairs.
That way if anyone is out there waiting for us,
and I reckon there will be,
they won't know which Harry Potter is the real one.
The real one?
I believe you're familiar with this particular brew.
- No, absolutely not. - I told you he'd take it well.
No, if you think I'm gonna let,
everyone risk their lives for me...
We've done if before, mate.
No, no, this is different.
Taking that, becoming me. No!
Well none of us really fancy it, mate.
Yeah, imagine if something went wrong,
and we be stuck as a screwy
specky gits, forever.
Everyone here is of age, Potter.
They've all agreed to take the risk.
Technically,
I'd been coerced
Mundungus Fletcher, Mr. Potter.
Always been a huge admirer.
Nip it, Mundungus.
Alright Granger, its discussed.
Blimey, Hermione!
Straight in here, if you please.
For those of you who haven't taken polyjuice potion before,
fair warning.
Tastes like goblin piss.
Have enough experiences with that, do you, Mad-eye?
Just trying to defuse the tension.
Wow! We're identical!
Not yet you're not.
Haven't you got anything a bit more sporting, have you?
Yeah, I don't really fancy this color.
Well fancy this, you're not you, so shove it, and strip.
Alright, Alright.
You need to change too, Potter.
Bill, look away, I'm hideous.
I knew she was lying about that tattoo.
Harry, your eyesight really is awful.
All right then, we'll be pairing off.
Each Potter will have a protector.
Mundungus, stick tight to me.
I want to keep an eye on ya.
- As for Harry... - Yes?
The real Harry. Where the devil are you anyway?
- Here. - You ride with Hagrid.
I brought you here 16 years ago,
when you were no bigger than a bow truckle.
Seems only right that
I should be the one that take you away now.
Yes, this is all very touching. Let's go!
Head for the Burrows. We rendezvous there.
- On the count of three! - Hold tight, Harry!
One!
Two!
Three!
Watch your right!
Hagrid, we have to help the others!
Can't do that, Harry.
Mad-Eye's orders.
Hang on!
Stupefy!
Hang on, Harry!
Hagrid!
No! No!
Harry!
Harry! Hagrid!
What happened?
Where are the others?
Is no one else back?
They were on us right from the start, Molly.
We didn't stand a chance.
Well, thank goodness you two are all right.
The Death Eaters were waiting for us. It was an ambush.
Ron and Bill should have already been back.
Dad and Fred as well.
Here.
Quick, into the house.
Oh My boy...
- Come here! - What are you doing?
What creature sat in the corner the
first time Harry Potter visited my office in Hogwarts.
- Are you mad? - What creature?
A Grindylow.
We have been betrayed.
Voldemort knew you were being moved tonight.
I had to make sure, you weren't an imposter.
Wait!
The last words Albus Dumbledore, spoke to the pair of us.
"Harry is the best hope we have. "
"Trust him. "
What gave you away?
Hedwig, I think.
She was trying to protect me.
Thanks.
He deserves that. Brilliant he was.
I wouldn't be standing here without him.
Really?
Why is it so a surprise?
We the last back? Where's George?
How are you feeling, Georgie?
- Saint like. - Come again?
Saint like.
I'm holey. I'm holey,
Fred! Get it?
A whole wide world of ear related humor
and you go for 'I'm holey".
That's pathetic.
Think I'm still better looking than you.
Mad-Eye's dead.
Mundungus took one look at Voldemort and disapparated.
Head for the burrow.
Seven, Seven...
- Horcruxes... - They could be hidden anywhere, couldn't they.
To tear the soul into seven pieces...
If we destroy the Horcruxes.
One destroys, Voldemort.
Harry...
- Do not lie to me. Do not lie to me. - No!
Going somewhere?
Nobody else is going to die.
Not for me.
For you?
You think Mad-Eye died for you?
You think George took that curse for you?
You maybe the chosen one, mate...
but this is a whole lot bigger than that.
Its always been bigger than that.
- Come with me. - And leave Hermione?
Are you mad?
We wouldn't last two days, without her.
Don't tell her I said that.
Besides, you still got the trace on you,
you still got the wedding...
I don't care about a wedding.
I'm sorry, no matter whose it is.
I have to start finding these Horcruxes.
They're our only chance, to beat him.
And the longer we stay here, the stronger he gets.
Tonight is not the night, mate.
You'll only be doing him a favor.
Do you think he knows?
I mean they are bits of his soul, these Horcruxes.
Pieces of him.
When Dumbledore destroyed the Ring,
you destroyed Tom Riddle's Diary.
He must have felt something.
To kill the other Horcruxes, we have to find them.
Where are they?
Where do we start?
Zip me up, will you?
It seems silly doesn't it, a wedding?
Given what's going on.
Maybe that's the best reason to have it.
Because of everything that's going on.
Morning.
All together now!
One! Two! Three!
How it looking your end, boys?
Brilliant.
Bloody, hell. What's the Minister of Magic doing here?
To what do we owe the pleasure, Minister?
I think we both know the answer to that question, Mr. Potter.
This is?
Herein it is set forth,
the last will and testament of,
Albus Percival Wulfric Brian Dumbledore.
"First, to Ronald Billius Weasley,
I leave my deluminlator. "
"A device, of my own making,
In the hope, that when things seem most dark...
It will show him the light. "
- Dumbledore left this for me? - Yeah.
Brilliant.
- What is it? - Open it.
Wicked.
"To Hermione Jean Granger,
I leave my copy of 'The Tales of Beedle the Bard'."
"In the hope that she find it entertaining and instructive "
My mom used to read me those.
The wizard and the hopping pot,
Babbity Rabbity and the Cackling Stump.
Come on. Babbity Rabbity.
No?
"To Harry James Potter
I leave the snitch he caught
"in his first
Quidditch match at Hogwarts.
As a reminder of the rewards of perseverance...
and skill. "
Is that it then?
Not quite.
Dumbledore left you,
a second bequest.
The sword of Godric Gryffindor.
Unfortunately, the sword of Gryffindor
was not Dumbledore's to give away.
As an important historical artifact it belongs...
to Harry.
It belongs to Harry.
It came to him when he most needed it
in the Chamber of Secrets.
The sword may present itself
to any worthy Gryffindor, Miss Granger,
that does not make it that wizards property.
And in any event,
the current whereabouts of the sword are unknown.
Excuse me?
The Sword is Missing.
I don't know what you are up, to, Mr. Potter,
but you can't fight this war on your own.
He's too strong.
Hello, Harry.
I've interrupted your deep thoughts, haven't I?
I see it growing small in your eyes.
Of course not. How are you, Luna?
Very well,
I've been bitten by garden a gnome and numbed my thumb.
Gnome saliva is very beneficial.
Xenophilius Lovegood.
We live just over the heel.
Nice to meet you, sir.
I trust you know Mr. Potter that we at the Quibbler,
disagree with the Daily Prophet,
and have always fully supported Dumbledore...
during his lifetime and in his death, support you just as fully.
Thank you.
Come Daddy. Harry doesn't want to talk to us right now.
He's just too polite to say so.
Excuse me, sir.
- May I sit down? - Mr. Potter.
By all means, here.
I found what you wrote in the Daily Prophet,
really moving.
You obviously knew Dumbledore well.
Well, I certainly knew him the longest.
Unless we don't count his brother Aberforth,
and somehow people never do seem to count, Aberforth.
I didn't even know he had a brother.
Dumbledore was always very private, even as a boy.
Do not despair, Elphias.
I'm told he's been thoroughly unrevealed by Rita Skeeter.
In 800 pages.
Word has it
that someone talked to her.
Someone who knew the Dumbledore family well.
Both you and I know who that is, Elphias.
A monstrous betrayal.
Who are, who are we talking about?
Bathilda Bagshot.
Who?
My god, boy. She is only the most...
celebrated magical historian of the last century.
She was as close to the Dumbledore's as anyone.
Oh, I'm sure Rita Skeeter
thought it well worth a trip to Godric's Hollow,
to take a peek into that old bird's records cage.
Godric's Hollow?
Bathilda Bagshot lives in Godric's Hallow?
That's where she first met, Dumbledore.
You don't mean to say he lived there too.
The family moved there
after his father killed those three Muggles.
It was quite the scandal.
Honestly my boy,
are you sure you knew him at all?
Ministry has fallen.
Minister of Magic, is dead.
They are coming.
Nice meeting you, Mr. Potter.
Ginny!
Go! Go!
Where are we?
Shaftesbury Avenue.
I used to come up here to theaters with mom and dad.
I don't know why I thought of it. It just popped into my head.
This way.
We need to change.
Bloody Hell
- Undetectable Extension charm. - You're amazing, you are.
Always a total surprise.
Ah, that'll be the books.
What about all the people at the wedding?
Do you think that we should go back?
They're after you, mate.
We'd put everyone in danger by going back.
- Ron's right. - Coffee
- A cappuccino please - You?
- What she said. - Same.
So where do we go from here? Leaky Cauldron.
It's too dangerous.
If Voldemort has taken over the Ministry,
none of the old places are safe.
Everyone from the wedding would have gone underground, into hiding.
My rucksack with all my things. I've left it at the burrow.
You're joking.
I had the essentials, packed for days. Just in case.
By the way, why're the jeans not my favourite?
Down!
Stupify!
Petrificus Totalus!
Go! Leave.
Lock the door, get the lights.
This one's names Rawl.
He was on the astronomy tower the last night they killed Dumbledore.
This is Dolohov.
I recognize him from the wanted notice.
So what we're gonna do with you, eh?
Kill us if it was turned round, wouldn't you?
We kill them, they'll know we were here.
- Ron. - Suppose he did Mad-eye? How would you feel then?
It's better we wipe their memories.
You're the boss. Hermione.
You're the best with spells.
Obliviate.
How is it they knew we were there?
Maybe you still have the trace on you?
They can't, the trace stays until I'm seventeen year's old.
What?
We didn't celebrate your birthday, Harry.
Ginny and I, we prepared a cake.
We were going to bring it out at the end of the wedding.
Hermione, honestly,
I appreciate the thought,
but really given the fact, that we were almost killed
by a couple of Death Eaters a few minutes ago.
Right... perspective.
We have to get off the streets, get to someplace safe.
What was that all about?
Probably Mad-Eye's idea.
In case Snape decides to come snooping.
Homenum Revelio.
We're alone.
Another wand!
I believe a different wand would work? I swear.
It should be another way.
Harry, where are you?
Is it dark up there?
Lovely.
Regulus Arcturus Black
R.A.B.
"I know I will be dead long before you read this. "
"I have stolen the real horcrux and intend to destroy it. "
R.A.B, he was Sirius' brother?
Yes.
The question is he didn't actually destroy the real Horcrux.
Spying on us, have you.
Kreacher, has been watching.
Maybe he knows where the real locket is?
Have you ever seen this before? Kreacher?
- It is Master Regulus's locket! - There were two, weren't there?
Where's the other one?
Kreacher doesn't know, about the other locket.
Yes, but did you ever see it? It was in this house.
Filthy mudblood that's what you are, Blood traitor Weasley!
Answer her.
Yes.
It was here,
in this house.
Most evil object.
How do you mean?
Before Master Regulus died, he ordered Kreacher to destroy,
but no matter how hard Kreacher tried, he could not do it.
Well, where is it now?
- Did someone take it? - He came in the night.
He took many things including the locket.
Who did? Who was it, Kreacher?
Mundungus.
Mundungus Fletcher.
Find him.
My father will hear about this.
Hey losers. He isn't here.
As your new Minister for Magic,
I promise to restore this temple of tolerance
to its former glory.
Therefore beginning today,
each employee will submit themselves,
for evaluation.
But know this, you have nothing to fear,
if you have nothing to hide.
They have flesh memories.
When Scrimgeour first gave it to you,
I thought, it might open at to your touch.
That Dumbledore hidden something inside it.
Harry Potter, how long it's been!
Get off me!
Expelliarmus!
What you playing at?
Setting a pair of bleeding house elves after me?
Dobby was only trying to help.
When Dobby saw Kreacher in Diagon Alley,
Which Dobby thought was curious.
And then Dobby heard Kreacher mention Harry Potter's name.
And then Dobby saw Kreacher talking with the thief.
Not a thief? You foul little...
git.
I'm a purveyor of rare and wondrous objects.
You're a thief, Dung, everyone knows it.
- Master Weasley, so good to see you. - Like your shoes.
Listen, I panicked that night, alright?
Can't help it if Mad-Eye fell off his broom.
- You. - Tell the truth.
When you turned this place over,
don't deny it,
you found a locket, am I right?
Why, was it valuable?
- So, was it? - He's worried he didn't get enough money for it.
Bleeding give it away, didn't I?
There I was plogging my wares in Diagon alley,
when some Ministry hag comes up and asks to see me license.
Says she the one would lock me up.
Would have done too, if she hadn't taken a fancy to that locket.
Who was it? The witch, do you know her?
Know her?
She's there. Look.
Bleedin' bone who.
Right, remember what we said.
Don't speak to anyone, unless absolutely necessary.
Just, try and act normal.
Do what everybody else is doing.
If we do that and with a bit of luck we'll get inside.
- And then... - It gets really tricky.
Correct.
- This is completely mental. - Completely.
The world's mental. Come on.
We have a Horcrux to find.
We flush ourselves in.
Its bloody disgusting.
- You, come along. - What, what?
What did I do?
- Are those...? - Muggles.
In their... rightful place.
Got to tell you, I'm starting to freak out a bit.
How long did you say this batch of polyjuice will last, Hermione?
I didn't.
Cattermole.
Its still raining inside my office. Its two days now.
Have you tried an umbrella?
Do you realize I'm going downstairs don't you, Cattermole?
- Downstairs? - To interrogate your wife.
Now if my wife's blood status were in doubt,
and the Head of Department
of Magical Law Enforcement needed a job doing,
I think I might just make that a priority.
You have one hour.
Oh my god, what am I gonna do?
My wife's all alone downstairs.
Ron, you don't have a wife.
Oh right.
Level Two.
But how do I stop it raining?
Try "Finite Incantatem".
This is you, Ron.
Finite Incantatem, okay.
And if that doesn't work?
I say if we don't locate Umbridge within the hour,
we go find Ron and come back another day.
- Deal? - Yes.
Ah, Mafalda. Trevor sent you, did he?
Good. We'll go straight down.
Albert, weren't you getting out?
Runcorn?
Accio locket!
All right, all right. Let's calm down.
Lets get back to work, please.
Calm down.
Runcorn?
Morning.
- Ron, it's me. - Harry!
Blimey! Forgot what you look like.
Where's Hermione?
She's gone down to the court rooms, with Umbridge.
Bloody cold down here.
I'm half blood. My father, my father was a wizard.
William Waldenten, he worked here for 30 years.
Perhaps you know him. He Always wore a jacket inside out.
There must be a mistake.
Tell the ministry, I must go to work, I'm half blood.
Mary Elizabeth Cattermole,
of 27 Chislehurst Gardens, Great Tolling, Itchum.
- Yes. - It's here.
Mother to Maisie, Ellie and Alfred; Wife to Reginald?
Regi.
Thank you, Albert.
Mary Elizabeth Cattermole.
Yes?
A wand was taken from you upon
your arrival at the Ministry today, Mrs. Cattermole
Is this that wand?
Would you please tell the court,
from which witch or wizard you took this wand?
I didn't take it.
I bought it at Diagon Alley, at Ollivanders, when I was 11.
It chose me.
You're lying.
Wands only choose witches, and you are not a witch.
But I am.
Tell them, Reg, tell them what I am.
Reg, tell them who I am.
What on earth are you doing, Albert?
You're lying, Dolores.
And one mustn't tell lies.
Stupefy!
Oh, it's Harry Potter!
It's him isn't it. This is one to tell the kids.
Expecto patronum!
Mary, go home.
Get the kids.
I'll meet you there.
We have to get out of the country, understand?
Mary, do as I say.
Mary?
Who's that?
Long story, nice meeting you.
- Harry Potter. - It's Harry, Harry Potter.
Expelliarmus!
Harry, Harry, quickly, in my bag.
There's a bottle labeled "Essence of Dittany".
Quickly!
Accio Dittany!
All right, unstopper it.
Hermione, his arm.
I know, just do it!
It's gonna... It's gonna sting a little bit.
What happened?
I thought we were going to go back to Grimmauld Place.
We were. Alright, One more, one more.
We were there we were there but, Yaxley had a hold of me,
I knew once he'd seen where we were we,
we couldn't stay so,
I brought us here, but,
Ron got splinched.
Protego Totalum.
- Salvio Hexia. - What are you doing?
Protective enchantments.
I don't fancy another visit
like the one we had at Shaftesbury Avenue, do you?
You can get going on a tent.
Tent?
- Protego Totalum. - Where am I supposed to find a tent?
Repello Muggletum. Muffliato.
You first.
Incendio.
Expulso!
Diffindo!
Reducto!
What are you doing?
We have to keep it safe, until we find out how to destroy it.
Seems strange, mate.
Dumbledore sent you off to find these Horcruxes,
but doesn't tell you how to destroy them.
Doesn't that bother you?
You know the spell, Harry.
- Tell me, Gregorovitch. - He stole from me.
Who was he, the thief?
The boy. It was he who took it.
I never saw it again, I swear on my life.
I believe you.
Avada Kedavra!
I thought it stopped.
You can't keep letting him in, Harry.
- You-Know-Who has found, Gregorovitch. - The Wand Maker?
He wants something that Gregorovitch used to have.
I don't know what. But he wants it desperately.
I mean, it's as if his life depends on it.
Don't, it comforts him.
It sets my teeth on edge.
What's he expecting to hear, good news?
I think he just hopes that he doesn't hear bad news.
How long before he can travel?
- I.. I'm doing everything I can. - You're not doing enough.
Take it off!
I said, Take it off, now!
- Better? - Right.
We'll take it in turns, okay?
Severus Snape voted in as headmaster of Hogwarts.
What's that?
What's that, smell?
Whatcha doing? It's heavy.
Oh I'm sorry. Do you want me to carry it?
Snatchers.
Good to know your enchantments work.
He could smell it, my perfume.
I told you,
Ron isn't strong enough to apparate.
Well then, we'll go on foot.
Only next time, as much as you like your perfume,
just don't wear any.
And now for the names of missing witches and wizards.
These are confirmed,
thankfully the list is short today.
Jason and Alison Denbright.
Oh, thank you.
Bella, Jake, Charlie, and Madge Farley.
Joe Laurie.
Eleanor Sarah Gibbs.
Harry and Bronwyn Trigg.
Rob and Ellie Dowson.
Georgia Clark-Day.
Joshua Flexson.
George Coutas.
Gabriella and Emily Mather.
Jacob and Mimi Erland.
William and Brian Gallagher.
He doesn't know what he's doing, does he?
None of us do.
Katie and James Killick.
Elsie Valentine Schroeder.
Jennifer Winston.
Tamsin and Iola Hillicker.
- Oh My God! - What?
I'll tell you in a minute.
Maybe you can tell me now.
Sword of Gryffindor. It's goblin made.
Brilliant.
No, you don't understand.
Dirt and rust have no effect on the blade.
It only takes in that which makes it stronger.
O... kay.
Harry, we've already destroyed one horcrux, right?
Tom Riddle's diary in the Chamber of Secrets.
With a basilisk fang.
If you tell me you've got one of those
in that bloody beaded bag of yours...
Don't you see?
In The Chamber of Secrets,
you stabbed the Basilisk with the sword of Gryffindor.
Its blade is impregnated with basilisk venom.
It only takes in that which makes it stronger.
- Exactly, which is why... - It can destroy Horcruxes.
That's why Dumbledore left it to you in his will.
You're brilliant, Hermione. Truly.
Actually, I'm highly logical
which allows me to slip past extraneous details.
And perceive clearly that which others overlook.
Yeah, there is only one problem with this.
The sword was stolen.
Yeah, I'm still here.
But you two carry on.
Don't let me spoil the fun.
- What's wrong? - Wrong? Nothing's wrong.
According to you, anyway.
If you got something to say, don't be shy.
Spit it out.
Alright, I'll spit it out.
But don't expect me to be grateful
just because now it's another damn thing we got to find.
I thought you knew what you signed up for.
Yeah, I thought it too.
I'm sorry. But I don't quite understand.
What part of this isn't living up to your expectations?
Did you think we were going to be staying in a five star hotel?
Finding a Horcrux every other day.
You thought you'd be back with your mum by Christmas?
I just thought, after all this time
we would actually have achieved something.
I thought you knew what you were doing.
I thought Dumbledore would have told you something worthwhile.
I thought you had a plan.
I told you everything Dumbledore told me.
And in case you haven't notice we have found a Horcrux already.
and we're as close to getting rid of it
as we are to finding the rest of them, aren't we?
Ron, Please, take off the Horcrux.
You wouldn't be saying any of this
if you hadn't been wearing it all day.
You don't know, why I listen to the radio every night, do you?
To make sure I don't hear Ginny's name,
or Fred, or George or Moms.
You think I'm not listening too?
You think I don't know how it feels?
No you don't know how it feels!
Your parents are dead! You have no family!
Stop! Stop!
- Let me go! - Go then!
Ron!
And you?
Are you coming or are you staying?
Fine, I get it. I saw you two the other night.
Ron there's... there's nothing.
Ron!
Ron, where are you going?
Come back!
Ron!
Salvia Hexia.
I open at the close.
Hermione. Hermione.
You were right. Snitches have flesh memories.
But I didn't catch the first snitch with my hand.
I almost swallowed it.
- "I open at the close. " - Yeah, what do you think that means?
I don't know.
I found something as well.
At first I thought it was an eye, but now I don't think it is.
It isn't a rune, and it isn't anywhere in Spellman's syllabary.
Somebody inked it in.
It isn't part of the book, somebody drew it.
Luna's dad was wearing it at Bill and Fleur's wedding.
Why would someone draw it in a children's book?
Hermione, I've been thinking.
I want to go to Godric's Hollow.
It's where I was born, It's where my parents died.
That's exactly where he'll expect you to go
because it means something to you.
But it means something to him too, Hermione.
You-Know-Who almost died there.
Isn't that exactly the type of place
he'd be likely to hide a Horcrux?
I... it's dangerous, Harry.
But even I have to admit
recently I've been thinking we have to go there.
I think it's possible something else is hidden there.
What?
The Sword.
If Dumbledore wanted you to find it,
and didn't want it to falling in to the Ministry hands,
where better to hide it than
the birthplace of the founder of Gryffindor.
Hermione.
Don't ever let me give you a haircut again.
I still think that we should use the Polyjuice Potion.
No, this is where I was born.
I'm not returning as someone else.
Harry, I think it's Christmas eve.
Listen.
Do you think they may be in there, Hermione?
My Mom and Dad.
Yeah, I think they would.
Ignotus Peverell.
Hey, Harry?
Merry Christmas, Hermione.
Merry Christmas, Harry.
Harry, there is someone watching us.
By the church.
I think I know who that is.
- I don't like this, Harry. - Hermione, she knew Dumbledore.
She might have the sword.
This is where they died, Hermione.
This is where he murdered them.
You're Bathilda, aren't you?
Here, let me do that.
Miss Bagshot, who is this man?
Harry.
Harry!
Are you feeling better?
You've outdone yourself this time, Hermione.
Forest of Dean.
I came here once with Mum and Dad. Years ago.
It's just how I remember it.
The trees, the river, everything.
Like nothings changed.
Not true of course, everything's changed.
If I brought my parents back here now,
they probably wouldn't recognize any of it.
Not the trees.
Not the river.
Not even me.
Maybe we should just stay here, Harry.
Grow old.
You wanted to know who was the boy in the photograph was.
I know.
Gellert Grindelwald.
He's the thief I saw in Gregorovitch's wand shop.
Speaking of which, where is my wand?
Where's my wand, Hermione?
As we were leaving Godrics Hollow
I cast a curse and it rebounded.
I'm sorry.
I tried to mend it, but wands are different.
It's done.
Leave me yours.
Go inside and get warm.
I'll take the locket as well.
Lumos.
Accio sword!
Diffindo.
Hermione?
Are you mental?
It was you.
Well yeah, bit obvious, I think.
And you cast the doe as well did you?
No, I thought that was you.
No, my Patronus was a stag.
Right, now that was...
Okay, Ron. Do it.
I can't handle it.
That thing affect me more than it effects you and Hermione.
- All the more reason. - No, I can't.
Then why are you here?
Why did you come back?
Now I'll have to speak to it in order for it to open.
When it does, don't hesitate.
I don't know what's in there, but it will put up a fight.
The bit of Riddle that was in that diary tried to kill me.
One.
Two.
Three.
I have seen your heart and it is mine.
I have seen your dreams, Ronald Weasley.
And I see your fears.
Least loved by your mother, who craved a daughter.
Least loved by the girl, who prefers your friend.
Ron, kill it!
We were better without you.
Happy without you.
Who would look at you? Who has, Harry Potter.
What are you, compared to the chosen one?
Ron, it's lying!
Your mother confessed, she would prefer me as a son.
What woman would take you?
You are nothing... nothing.
Nothing compared to him.
Just think.
There are only three to go.
Hermione?
Is everything alright?
It's fine. Actually, yeah, it's more than fine.
Hey.
You...
...A complete ass, Ronald Weasley!
You show up here after weeks and you say 'hey'?
Where's my wand, Harry?
- Where's my wand? - I don't know.
Harry Potter. You give me my wand!
- How come he's got your wand? - Never mind why's he got my wand.
What is that?
You destroyed it.
And how is it that you just
happen to have the sword of Gryffindor?
It's a long story.
Don't think this changes anything.
Of course not. I only just destroyed a bloody Horcrux,
why will that change anything.
Look, I wanted to come back as soon as I left.
I just didn't know how to find you.
Yeah, how did you find us?
With this. Doesn't just turn off lights.
I don't know how it works,
but Christmas morning I sleeping in this little pub.
Keeping away from some snatchers.
- When I heard it. - It?
A voice.
Your voice, Hermione.
Comin' out of it.
And what exactly did I say if I may ask?
My name.
Just my name.
Like a whisper.
So I took it, clicked it...
and this tiny ball of light appeared.
And I knew, sure enough.
It floated towards me, the ball of light.
Went right to my chest, straight through me. Right here.
I knew it was gonna take me where I needed to go,
so I disapparated.
I came to this hillside.
It was dark, I had no idea where I was.
I just hoped that one of you would show yourself.
You did.
I've always liked these flames Hermione makes.
How long do you reckon she'll stay mad at me?
Just keep talking about that little ball of light touching your heart.
- And she'll come around. - It's true. Every word.
This is gonna sound crazy.
But I think, thats why Dumbledore left it to me.
The Deluminator.
I think he knew that somehow I'd need to find my way back.
That she'd lead me.
You know, I just realized. You need a wand, don't you?
- Yeah. - I got one here.
It's a Blackthorn, 10 inches, nothing special.
I reckon it'll do.
Took it off a snatcher a couple of weeks ago.
Don't tell Hermione this.
They're a bit dim, snatchers.
This one is definitely partial to smelling.
- Engorgio. - Put it out.
What's going on in there?
- Nothing! - Nothing!
We need to talk.
Yeah, alright.
I want to go see Xenophilius Lovegood.
Sorry?
See this? It's a letter Dumbledore wrote to Grindelwald.
Look at the signature.
It's the mark again.
It keeps cropping up.
In Beedle the Bard, in the graveyard in Godric's Hollow.
It was there too.
- Where? - Outside Gregorvitch's wand shop.
- What does it mean? - Look.
You've got no idea where the next Horcrux is, and neither do I.
But this, this means something.
I'm sure of it.
Yeah. Hermione's right.
We ought to see Lovegood.
Let's vote on it.
Those in favor.
You're not still mad at him, are you?
I'm always mad at him.
Luna, we're here.
Keep off the Dirigible Plums.
What is it? Who are you?
What do you want?
Hello, Mr. Lovegood.
I'm Harry Potter, we met a few months ago.
Can we come in?
- Where is Luna? - Luna?
She'll be along.
So, how can I help you, Mr. Potter?
Well, actually,
it was about something you were wearing around your neck at the wedding.
It was a symbol.
- You mean this? - Yes.
That's it exactly.
What we wondered is... what is it?
What is it?
Well, it's the sign of the Deathly Hallows, of course.
- The What? - The What?
The Deathly Hallows.
I assume you are all familiar with the tale of the three brothers.
- Yes... - Yes.
No.
I have it in here.
There were once three brothers,
who were traveling along a lonely winding road...
- At twilight. - Midnight.
Mom always said midnight.
Twilight's fine, better actually.
- Do you want to read it? - Uh, no.
There were once three brothers, who were traveling along...
a lonely winding road...
At twilight.
In time the brothers reached
a river too treacherous to pass.
But they were learned in the magical arts,
the three brothers simply waved their wands, and made a bridge.
Before they could cross however,
they found their path blocked by a hooded figure.
It was Death.
And he felt cheated.
Cheated,
because travelers would always drown in the river.
But Death was cunning.
He pretended to congratulate the three brothers on their magic.
And said, that each had earned a prize for having
been clever enough to evade him.
The oldest asked for a wand, more powerful than any in existence.
So death fashioned him a
wand from an elder tree that stood nearby.
The second brother decided he wanted to humiliate death even further,
and asked for the power to recall loved ones from the grave.
So Death plucked a stone from the river and offered it to him.
Finally, Death turned to the third brother.
A humble man,
he asked for something that would allow him to go forth from that place,
without being followed by death.
And so it was that death reluctantly handed over his own cloak of invisibility.
The first brother traveled to a distant village.
While with the elder wand in hand,
he killed a wizard with whom he had once quarrels.
Drunk with the power that the
elder wand had given him.
He bragged of his invincibility.
But that night...
Another wizard stole the wand
and slit the brother's throat for good measure.
And so death took the first brother for his own.
The second brother journeyed to his home.
Where he took the stone and turned it twice in hand.
To his delight
the girl he'd once hoped to marry before her untimely death,
appeared before him.
Yet soon she turned sad and cold
for she did not belong in the mortal world.
Driven mad with hopeless longing,
the second brother killed himself so as to join her.
And so death took the second brother.
As for the third brother, Death searched for many years
but was never able to find him.
Only when he had attained a great age did the youngest brother,
shed the cloak of invisibility and give it to his son.
He then greeted death as a old friend
and went with him gladly departing this life as equals.
So there you are. Those are the Deathly Hallows.
I'm sorry sir, I still don't quite understand.
The Elder wand.
The most powerful wand ever made.
The resurrection stone.
The cloak of invisibility.
Together, they make the Deathly Hallows.
Together, they make one master of death.
That mark was on the grave in Godrics Hollow.
Um, Mr. Lovegood,
does the Peverell family
have anything to do with the Deathly Hallows?
Ignotus, excuse me. And his brothers Cadmus and Antioch,
thought to be the original owners of the Hallows,
and therefore the inspiration for the story.
But your tea has gone cold.
I'll be right back.
Let's get out of here.
I don't want to drink anymore of that stuff.
Hot or cold.
- Thank you, Sir. - You forgot the water.
- Water? - For the tea.
How silly of me.
It's really nice sir, but we really should be going any way.
No, you do not!
Sir?
You're my only hope.
They were angry, you see, from what I've been writing.
So they took her.
They took my children.
My children.
Oh, it's really you, then it'll work.
Who took her, sir?
Voldemort.
I got him!
Treacherous little bleeder!
Is there no one we can trust?
They kidnapped her because he supported me.
He was just desperate.
I'll do the enchantments.
Hello, beautiful.
Well, don't hang about. Snatch 'em.
Harry. Tell me what to do.
Tell me, where it is.
Grindelwald. Grindelwald.
I knew you'd come, one day.
But surely you must know.
I no longer have what you seek.
Tell me, Grindelwald, tell me where it is.
Tell me who possesses it.
The elder wand lies with him, of course.
Buried in the earth.
Dumbledore.
The Hallows exist.
But he's only after one of them, the last one.
He knows where it is.
He's gonna have it by the end of the night.
You know who's had the elder wand?
- Don't touch her! - Leave him.
Your boyfriend will get much worse
than that if he doesn't learn to behave himself.
What happened to you, ugly?
No, not you.
- What's your name? - Dudley. Vernon Dudley.
Check it.
And you, my lovely.
What do they call you?
Penelope Clearwater, half-blood.
There's no Vernon Dudley on here.
You hear that ugly? This says you're lying.
How come you don't want us to know who you are?
It's wrong, I told you who I am.
Change of plan.
We're not taking this lot to the Ministry.
Get, Draco.
Well?
I can't be sure.
Look closely, son.
If we are the ones to hand Potter over to the Dark Lord.
Everything would be forgiven,
it would be as it was, understand?
Now we won't be forgetting who really actually caught him.
I hope, Mr. Malfoy.
- You dare to talk to me like that in my own house! - Lucius!
Do not be shy, sweetie. Come closer.
Now, if this isn't who you think it is, Draco,
and we call Him. He'll kill us all.
We need to be absolutely sure.
- What's wrong with his face? - Yes, what is wrong with his face?
He came to us like that.
Something he picked up in the forest, I reckon.
An interesting jinx. Was it you, dear?
Give me her wand,
let's see what your last spell was.
Got you.
What's that?
Where'd you get that from?
It was in her bag when we searched her.
I reckon it's mine now.
Are you mad?
Get out! Get out!
Cissy, put the boys in the cellar.
I want a conversation with this one.
Girl to girl!
What are we gonna do?
We can't leave Hermione alone with her.
Ron?
Harry?
Luna?
That Sword is meant to be in my vault now,
how did you get it?
Did you and your friend's take it from my vault?
I didn't take anything!
I don't believe you.
- We have to do something! - There is no way out of here.
We tried everything. It's enchanted.
You're bleeding, Harry.
That's a curious thing to keep on yourself.
Help us!
- Let her go. - You go, get back!
You, Goblin. Come with me.
Dobby? What are you doing here?
Dobby's come to rescue, Harry Potter of course.
Dobby will always be there for Harry Potter.
Are you saying that you can apparate in and out of this room?
Could you take us with you?
Of course, sir, I'm a elf.
Works for me.
Right, Dobby, I want you to take Luna and Mr. Ollivander...
Shell Cottage, on the outskirts of Tinworth.
Trust me.
When ever you're ready, sir.
Sir? I like her very much!
Meet me at top of the stairs in ten seconds.
Who gets his wand?
I'm going to ask you once more, goblin.
Think very, very carefully.
- How did they get there? - I don't know.
You don't know? Why were you doing your job?
Who got into my vault?
Who stole it?
Who... Stole it?
It's impossible to break into Gringotts, the sword is there.
Then how is it that it's out then?
There is no place safer, than Gringotts.
Liar!
Consider yourself lucky, goblin.
- The same won't be said for this one. - Like hell!
Expelliarmus.
Stupefy!
Stop!
Drop your wands.
I said, drop them!
Pick 'em up, Draco, now! Well, well, well.
Look what we have here.
It's Harry Potter.
He's all bright, shiny and new again.
Just in time for the Dark Lord.
Call him.
Stupefy!
Stupid elf! You could have kill me!
Dobby never meant to kill.
Dobby only meant to maim or seriously injure.
How dare you take a witch's wand.
How dare you defy your masters.
Dobby has no master.
Dobby is a free elf.
And Dobby has come to save Harry Potter and his friends.
Hermione, are you all right?
We're safe. We're all safe.
Harry Potter...
Dobby!
Dobby, you're all right then, hold on.
Hold on, okay?
Just hold on, okay? We're going to fix it.
Hermione, you have something...
In your bag. Hermione!
Come on.
Help me.
Such a beautiful place,
to be with friends.
Dobby is happy,
to be with be with his friend,
Harry Potter.
We should close his eyes.
Don't you think?
There, now he could be sleeping.
I want to bury him.
Properly, without magic.